Survival is her only option
Frenzy is a horror, thriller, tv movie film directed by Jose Montesinos.
A group of friends run a popular travel vlog that helps fund their adventures.
The leader of the group brings along her younger sister for
the next scuba diving trip to an isolated cove.
But when their plane crashes, the two sisters must use their strength,
resourcefulness and immense courage to survive a pack of great white sharks.
Lindsey, played by Aubrey Reynolds.
Paige, played by Gina Vitori.
Kahaia, played by Lanett Tachel.
Seb, played by Taylor Jorgensen.
Evan, played by Michael S. New.
Island Pilot, played by Pope Bustos.
Frenzy is a 1972 British neo-noir thriller film directed by Alfred
Hitchcock in the penultimate feature film of his extensive career.
The screenplay by Anthony Shaffer is based on the 1966 novel Goodbye
Piccadilly, Farewell Leicester Square by Arthur La Bern.
The film stars Jon Finch, Alec McCowen and Barry Foster and features Billie Whitelaw,
Anna Massey, Barbara Leigh-Hunt, Bernard Cribbins and Vivien Merchant.
The original music score was composed by Ron Goodwin.
The plot centres on a serial killer in contemporary London
and the ex-RAF serviceman he implicates.
In a very early scene there is dialogue that mentions two actual London serial murder cases:
the Christie murders in the 1940s–1950s and the Jack the Ripper murders in 1888.
Frenzy was the third and final film that Hitchcock made in
Britain after he moved to Hollywood in 1939.
The other two were Under Capricorn (1949) and Stage Fright (1950).
The last film he made in Britain before his move to the
United States was Jamaica Inn (1939).
Frenzy was the only Hitchcock film given an R rating in the
United States during its initial release.
Frenzy was screened at the 1972 Cannes Film Festival, but it
was not entered into the main competition.
Some critics—such as Raymond Foery, author of Alfred Hitchcock's Frenzy: The Last Masterpiece—consider Frenzy the last
great Hitchcock film, and a return to form after his two previous works: Torn Curtain (1966) and Topaz (1969).
The film was a commercial success, grossing $12.6 million at the box office worldwide ($96.9
million with 2025 inflation) from a $2 million ($15.3 million in 2025 inflation) budget.
The film explores themes of shark attack, shark,
survival horror, plane crash, sea plane.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and intense.